<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Koronavilkku</string>

    <string name="all_next">Next</string>
    <string name="all_previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="all_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="all_thl_image_description">Finnish Institute for Health and Welfare</string>
    <string name="all_today">today</string>
    <string name="all_yesterday">yesterday</string>
    <string name="all_date_and_time">%1$s at %2$s</string>
    <string name="all_date_range" translatable="false">%1$s\u2013%2$s</string>
    <string name="all_finnish" translatable="false">Suomi</string>
    <string name="all_swedish" translatable="false">Svenska</string>
    <string name="all_english" translatable="false">English</string>
    <string name="all_app_additional_info">More information about Koronavilkku</string>
    <string name="all_system_enable">Enable</string>
    <string name="all_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="all_allow">Allow</string>
    <string name="all_deny">Deny</string>
    <string name="all_close">Close</string>
    <string name="all_continue">Continue</string>

    <string name="diagnosis_title">Report your infection</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_body1">You will need a key code to report your infection. You will receive a key code from a healthcare professional or via text message from the Finnish Institute for Health and Welfare.</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_body2">Enter the key code on the phone you usually carry with you. Koronavilkku indicates potential exposure to users who have been close to you during the period when you could have infected others. The key code does not reveal your identity.</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_page_title">Report your infection</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_code_entry">Report your infection</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_en_disabled">Exposure notifications must be turned on to report an infection. Enable exposure notifications in the Koronavilkku Home view.</string>

    <string name="diagnosis_locked_title">You have already reported your infection</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_locked_body1">The information you have reported will help to tackle the coronavirus epidemic. The app is now locked and no longer collects information about nearby phones. We wish you a quick recovery!</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_locked_image_description">Locked</string>

    <string name="code_entry_title">Enter your key code</string>
    <string name="code_entry_submit">Send</string>
    <string name="code_entry_invalid">The key code is invalid or has expired. Please check that you have entered the exact code you received.</string>
    <string name="code_entry_submit_failed">Failed to report infection because the server cannot be reached. Please check your internet connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="code_entry_en_disabled">Exposure notifications must be turned on to report an infection. Enable exposure notifications in the Koronavilkku Home view.</string>
    <string name="code_entry_info">The key code does not reveal your identity.</string>

    <string name="diagnosis_complete_title">Thank you for your report</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_complete_body">The information you have reported will help to tackle the coronavirus epidemic. The app is now locked and no longer collects information about nearby phones. We wish you a quick recovery!</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_complete_continue">OK</string>

    <string name="home_title">Home</string>
    <string name="home_exposure_label">Potential exposure</string>
    <string name="home_no_exposure_label">No observed exposures</string>
    <string name="home_pending_check_label">Checking for potential exposures has not been carried out for over 24 hours. The app will try again later. You can start a check now.</string>
    <string name="home_exposure_sub_label">You may have been exposed to the coronavirus</string>
    <string name="home_no_exposure_sub_label">You have not been near a person who has reported an infection</string>
    <string name="home_exposure_instructions">See instructions</string>
    <string name="home_exposure_check">Check now</string>
    <string name="home_notifications_unknown" translatable="false">!</string>
    <string name="home_show_notification_guide">If you receive an exposure notification follow these instructions</string>

    <string name="home_symptom_label">Do you think you may have COVID-19?</string>
    <string name="home_prevention_label">How to protect yourself from an infection</string>
    <string name="home_prevention_url">https://thl.fi/en/web/infectious-diseases-and-vaccinations/what-s-new/coronavirus-covid-19-latest-updates/transmission-and-protection-coronavirus</string>
    <string name="home_statistics_label">COVID-19 in Finland</string>
    <string name="home_statistics_url">https://thl.fi/en/web/infectious-diseases-and-vaccinations/what-s-new/coronavirus-covid-19-latest-updates/situation-update-on-coronavirus</string>
    <string name="home_thl_url">https://thl.fi/en/web/thlfi-en</string>

    <string name="home_status_system_enabled">Koronavilkku is active</string>
    <string name="home_status_system_disabled">Koronavilkku is disabled</string>
    <string name="home_status_system_locked">Koronavilkku is locked</string>

    <string name="home_symptom_sub_label">Take an online medical COVID-19 symptom check-up</string>
    <string name="home_app_guide">About Koronavilkku</string>

    <string name="home_status_disabled_explained">Re-enable exposure notifications.</string>
    <string name="home_status_enabled_explained">The app works even if you close it.</string>
    <string name="home_status_locked_explained">Thank you for reporting your infection. The app will no longer collect information about encounters. We wish you a quick recovery!</string>

    <string name="symptoms_title">COVID-19 symptom assessment</string>
    <string name="symptoms_info">If you suspect that you have COVID-19, take an online COVID-19 symptom assessment in the Omaolo service. You will receive additional instructions based on your answers. It takes approximately 10 minutes to complete the assessment.</string>
    <string name="symptoms_link_title">Take a symptom assessment in the Omaolo service</string>
    <string name="symptoms_link">https://www.omaolo.fi/palvelut/oirearviot/649?lang=en</string>
    <string name="symptoms_link_name">omaolo.fi</string>

    <string name="settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_about_subtitle">About the app</string>
    <string name="settings_status_item">Exposure notifications</string>
    <string name="settings_status_on">Enabled</string>
    <string name="settings_status_off">Disabled</string>
    <string name="settings_status_locked">Locked</string>
    <string name="settings_tos_item">Terms of use</string>
    <string name="settings_guide_item">How Koronavilkku works</string>
    <string name="settings_faq_item">Frequently asked questions</string>
    <string name="settings_faq_link_url">https://koronavilkku.fi/en/faq/</string>
    <string name="settings_faq_link_name">koronavilkku.fi</string>

    <string name="settings_privacy_item">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="settings_privacy_link_url">https://koronavilkku.fi/en/privacy/</string>
    <string name="settings_version">%1$s %2$s</string>
    <string name="settings_privacy_link_name">koronavilkku.fi</string>
    <string name="settings_terms_link_name">koronavilkku.fi</string>
    <string name="settings_language_item">Change app language</string>
    <string name="settings_open_source_notices">Open source licenses</string>

    <string name="terms_url">https://koronavilkku.fi/en/terms/</string>

    <string name="exposure_detail_title">Potential exposure</string>

    <string name="exposure_detail_message">In the past 14 days, you have been close to a person who has reported a COVID-19 infection.</string>

    <string name="exposure_detail_contact_title">Contact healthcare services</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_contact_subtitle">Contact healthcare services even if you do not have any symptoms consistent with COVID-19. Healthcare services will give you instructions and evaluate your need for a coronavirus test.</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_contact_start">Contact</string>

    <string name="exposure_detail_title_none">No observed exposures</string>

    <string name="exposure_detail_message_none">Koronavilkku has not detected exposures to the coronavirus in the last 14 days.</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_disclaimer_none">However, the application is not able to identify every situation where exposure may occur.</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_last_check">Last checked %s</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_no_last_check">No checks yet</string>

    <string name="exposure_detail_notifications_title">Show exposure notifications</string>

    <string name="exposure_detail_instructions_title">What should I do?</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_instructions_subtitle">Follow the instructions below for 14 days. Continue to follow the instructions even if you receive a negative coronavirus test result.</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_instructions_1">Monitor your health. If you develop any symptom consistent with COVID-19, get tested for the coronavirus even if you have already been tested. Symptoms consistent with COVID-19 are change in sense of smell or taste, shortness of breath, cough, sore throat, runny nose, fever, headaches, muscle pain, unexplained diarrhoea or abdominal pain.</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_instructions_2">Avoid meeting other people.</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_instructions_3">Maintain good hand hygiene.</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_instructions_4">Avoid public places and public transport. If you have to visit public places, keep at least a two-meter distance to other people. Also use a face mask.</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_instructions_5">If possible, let someone else handle food shopping and other errands outside the home.</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_instructions_6">If you cough or sneeze, use a disposable tissue to cover your mouth and nose. Put the used tissue in a waste bin and wash your hands with water and soap or use hand sanitiser. If you do not have a tissue, cough or sneeze into your sleeve.</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_instructions_7">Work remotely if possible.</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_instructions_8">If you are not in Finland, follow any instructions given by local authorities.</string>

    <string name="exposure_detail_more_instructions_title">See more detailed instructions</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_more_instructions_link_name">thl.fi</string>
    <string name="exposure_detail_more_instructions_link">https://thl.fi/en/web/infectious-diseases-and-vaccinations/what-s-new/coronavirus-covid-19-latest-updates/symptoms-and-treatment-coronavirus</string>

    <string name="exposure_detail_app_info">About Koronavilkku</string>

    <string name="notification_list_title">Exposure notifications</string>
    <string name="notification_list_disclaimer">The assessment of your exposure is based on encounters that Koronavilkku has collected during the last 14 days. The intensity of exposure cannot be accurately assessed.</string>

    <string name="notification_item_title">Notification about potential exposure %s</string>
    <string name="notification_item_count_label">Potential exposures:</string>
    <string name="notification_item_time_range_label">Time period:</string>

    <string name="guide_title">"About Koronavilkku "</string>
    <string name="guide_p1_text">Koronavilkku is an application produced by the Finnish Institute for Health and Welfare that informs you if it estimates that you may have been exposed to the coronavirus. If you are diagnosed with COVID-19, you can report this anonymously using the app. Your privacy is strongly protected.</string>

    <string name="guide_code_title">Each phone receives a random code</string>
    <string name="guide_code_text">The application generates an ID code for each phone. The code is random and changes several times an hour to ensure your privacy. The ID code does not contain information about you or your phone.</string>

    <string name="guide_exchange_title">Phones swap codes with each other</string>
    <string name="guide_exchange_text">When close enough to each other, the apps swap codes through a Bluetooth signal. This allows the application to keep track of encounters without saving users\' identity or location data.</string>

    <string name="guide_infection_title">If you are diagnosed with COVID-19</string>
    <string name="guide_infection_text">If you are diagnosed with COVID-19, you will receive a key code from your healthcare professional. You can use this code to report your infection through the app. If you report your infection, the app sends your phone\'s ID codes to the server. No personal or location information is sent with the ID codes, so you will remain anonymous.</string>

    <string name="guide_check_title">The app compares codes</string>
    <string name="guide_check_text">Koronavilkku downloads a list of codes from the server several times a day. The list contains the codes of the phones that have been used to report a COVID-19 infection through the app. Koronavilkku compares these codes to the codes your phone has collected from other app users. This enables the app to determine whether you have been near an infected person.</string>

    <string name="guide_notification_title">You receive a notification of potential exposure</string>
    <string name="guide_notification_text">If the codes collected by your phone match those received from people who have reported a COVID-19 infection, you will be notified of a potential exposure. You can then provide your contact information to healthcare professionals and receive further instructions.\n\nIf you think that you may have COVID-19, you can take a symptom assessment at any time in the Omaolo.fi web service.</string>

    <string name="guide_privacy_title">Your privacy is protected</string>
    <string name="guide_privacy_body">The app protects your privacy in the following ways:</string>
    <string name="guide_privacy_item1">The information on encounters is stored only on your device. The stored data is deleted within 21 days, and it is deleted immediately if you remove the app.</string>
    <string name="guide_privacy_item2">Your identity is encrypted using random IDs.</string>
    <string name="guide_privacy_item3">The app never saves your phone\'s location information.</string>

    <string name="guide_button_back">Back</string>

    <string name="disable_title">COVID-19 exposure notifications are enabled</string>
    <string name="disable_subtitle">Do you need to disable exposure notifications?</string>
    <string name="disable_body">In some situations, it may be necessary to temporarily disable exposure notifications. This may be the case, for example, if you are a healthcare professional and do not want to use the application at your workplace.\n\nIf you disable exposure notifications, the application will stop working.</string>
    <string name="disable_note">To protect your health and the health of your loved ones, it is recommended that you disable exposure notifications only if it is really necessary. Remember to enable them again as soon as possible.</string>
    <string name="disable_turn_off_note">Disable COVID-19 exposure notifications</string>
    <string name="disable_button_turn_off">Disable</string>

    <string name="disable_confirm_title">Are you sure you want to disable exposure notifications?</string>
    <string name="disable_confirm_message">If you disable exposure notifications, Koronavilkku will not be able to notify you of potential exposure to the coronavirus.</string>

    <string name="enable_title">COVID-19 exposure notifications are disabled</string>

    <string name="enable_body">Because exposure notifications are disabled, Koronavilkku is not currently monitoring nearby phones.</string>
    <string name="enable_alert">To protect your health and the health of your loved ones, it is recommended that you enable exposure notifications as soon as possible.</string>
    <string name="enable_note">Enable COVID-19 exposure notifications</string>

    <string name="enable_err_title">Exposure notifications could not be turned on</string>
    <string name="enable_err_hms_location_permission">You must allow Huawei\'s HMS Core services to use the location of your phone in order to enable exposure notifications. You can allow this in your phone\'s settings.</string>
    <string name="enable_err_hms_update_required">You must update Huawei\'s HMS Core via App Gallery in order to enable exposure notifications.</string>
    <string name="enable_err_missing_capability">Your device is not supported</string>
    <string name="enable_err_api_not_supported">Unfortunately Google Play Services exposure notifications are not available for your device.\n\n%s</string>
    <string name="enable_err_not_owner">You are not logged into your phone as the device owner. Koronavilkku only works with the device owner\'s user profile.\n\nYou can switch between profiles by swiping down from the top of the home screen with two fingers and tapping the Switch User button.</string>
    <string name="enable_err_api_connection_device">Error: Your device is not supported.</string>
    <string name="enable_err_api_connection_unauthorized">Error: The app is not allowed to turn on exposure notifications.</string>
    <string name="enable_err_api_connection_generic">Error code: %d</string>
    <string name="enable_err_generic">Unknown error</string>
    <string name="enable_error_api_code">An unexpected exception occurred, error code: %1$d (%2$d)</string>
    <string name="enable_err_dismiss">Close</string>
    <string name="enable_err_hms_update">Update now</string>

    <string name="onboarding_done">Set-up complete!</string>

    <string name="intro_header_title">Thank you for installing Koronavilkku</string>
    <string name="intro_header_body">Koronavilkku is an application produced by the Finnish Institute for Health and Welfare. It aims to prevent the spread of COVID-19 disease. Your privacy is strongly protected in the application.</string>

    <string name="concept_header_title">How the app works</string>
    <string name="concept_header_body">Koronavilkku looks for nearby phones that have the same app installed. If someone you have previously met reports via Koronavilkku that they have COVID-19 disease, you receive an exposure notification. If you are diagnosed with COVID-19 disease, you can report this anonymously using the app.</string>

    <string name="accept_terms_header_title">Your privacy is protected</string>
    <string name="accept_terms_header_body">Koronavilkku protects your data and privacy in several ways.</string>
    <string name="accept_terms_personal_title">About personal information</string>
    <string name="accept_terms_personal_text">Koronavilkku does not store your name, date of birth or contact information. It cannot determine your identity or the identity of the people you come close to.\n\nThe application does not collect location data.</string>
    <string name="accept_terms_usage_title">How the app uses your data</string>
    <string name="accept_terms_usage_text">The app informs the server that the app is running. If you contact healthcare services through the app, the app will also provide information that you may have been exposed to COVID-19.\n\nAll communication between Koronavilkku and the server is encrypted.\n\nThe data is stored anonymously on a server located in Finland, and this server is managed by public administration bodies. The information system is only in use for the period specified in the Communicable Diseases Act. The information system and its data will be deleted when the system is no longer needed.</string>
    <string name="accept_terms_voluntary_title">Use is voluntary</string>
    <string name="accept_terms_voluntary_text">You do not have to use Koronavilkku. You can stop using it at any time by removing the app from your phone.</string>

    <string name="accept_terms_tos_text">I have read and agree to the terms of use for the service.</string>
    <string name="accept_terms_tos_link_text">Read the terms of use</string>
    <string name="accept_terms_activation_text">I am voluntarily starting to use the application</string>
    <string name="accept_terms_button_enable">Start using the app</string>
    <string name="accept_terms_scroll">Scroll down</string>

    <string name="en_blocked_title">Exposure notifications are off</string>
    <string name="en_blocked_body">Koronavilkku will not work unless you turn on the exposure notifications in your phone’s operating system. Start by pressing the Enable button below.</string>
    <string name="en_blocked_location">On some Android phones, exposure notifications also require that the location setting is turned on. The app does not, however, use your location data.</string>
    <string name="en_blocked_button_label">Enable</string>

    <string name="municipality_list_title">Select municipality</string>
    <string name="municipality_search_hint">Search</string>
    <string name="municipality_no_results">"No municipality found "</string>


    <string name="contact_evaluation_title">Contact healthcare via the Omaolo symptom assessment</string>
    <string name="contact_evaluation_body">Complete a symptom assessment in the Omaolo service; after this, you will be given instructions and an evaluation of whether you need a coronavirus test.  Complete a symptom assessment even if you do not have any symptoms suitable for the coronavirus disease. Filling in the symptom checker takes approximately 5–10 minutes.</string>
    <string name="contact_evaluation_start">Take assessment</string>
    <string name="contact_evaluation_footer">If you are under 15 years old, ask your guardian to use Omaolo on your behalf.</string>
    <string name="contact_evaluation_other_title">Other contact methods</string>
    <string name="contact_evaluation_other_sub_title">Alternatively, you can contact the municipal healthcare services in another way:</string>
    <string name="card_contact_request_title">Send a contact request</string>
    <string name="card_contact_request_link_name">Only for people without symptoms (not for children under 15)</string>
    <string name="contact_title">Contact healthcare services</string>
    <string name="contact_body">Contact healthcare services even if you do not have any symptoms consistent with COVID-19. Healthcare services will give you instructions and evaluate your need for a coronavirus test.</string>
    <string name="contact_instructions_title">First contact healthcare services by phone or online</string>
    <string name="contact_instructions_body">Contact healthcare services by phone or online before going to a healthcare facility.\n\nIf your condition is very poor, contact an emergency clinic. If your life is in danger, call the emergency number 112.</string>

    <string name="info_icon">Info</string>

    <string name="test_title" translatable="false">Testi</string>
    <string name="test_update_exposures" translatable="false">Luo simuloitu altistus</string>
    <string name="test_update_exposures_message" translatable="false">Hei, altistus tulee 5 sekunnin päästä</string>
    <string name="test_reset_onboarding" translatable="false">Aloita onboarding</string>
    <string name="test_download" translatable="false">Lataa avaimet nyt</string>
    <string name="test_download_message" translatable="false">Hei, lataus 5 sekunnin päästä</string>
    <string name="test_set_batch_id" translatable="false">Aseta</string>
    <string name="test_batch_id_hint" translatable="false">Batch id</string>
    <string name="test_clear_exposures" translatable="false">Poista altistukset</string>
    <string name="test_lock" translatable="false">Aseta lukitustila</string>
    <string name="test_unlock" translatable="false">Poista lukitustila</string>
    <string name="test_set_old_update" translatable="false">Aseta päivitys vanhaksi</string>
    <string name="test_open_en_settings" translatable="false">EN asetukset</string>
    <string name="test_check_play_services" translatable="false">Play services tarkistus</string>
    <string name="test_update_municipalities" translatable="false">Päivitä kuntalista</string>

    <string name="pre_web_contact_title_evaluation">Omaolo symptom assessment</string>
    <string name="pre_web_contact_title_no_evaluation">Send a contact request</string>
    <string name="pre_web_contact_body_evaluation">You can take the symptom assessment in the following languages. Select a language. You will then be taken to the Omaolo.fi web service. It takes approximately 5–10 minutes to take a symptom assessment.</string>
    <string name="pre_web_contact_body_no_evaluation">If you don\'t have symptoms, you can send a contact request via the Omaolo.fi web service. Select the language for the service. You will then be taken to the Omaolo.fi web service.</string>
    <string name="pre_web_contact_title">Select language</string>

    <string name="omaolo_link_failed_title">Omaolo.fi cannot not be opened</string>
    <string name="omaolo_link_failed_message">Koronavilkku can\'t direct you to the Omaolo.fi web service because your phone does not have an internet browser or its use has been blocked. Please contact health services by telephone.</string>

    <string name="municipality_load_failed">Error loading municipality list. Please check your internet connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="municipality_retry_load">Try again</string>

    <string name="onboarding_select_language_button" translatable="false">Language</string>
    <string name="select_language_title">Change app language</string>
    <string name="select_language_item_finnish" translatable="false">Suomi</string>
    <string name="select_language_item_swedish" translatable="false">Svenska</string>
    <string name="select_language_item_english" translatable="false">English</string>
    <string name="select_language_item_system_default">Device default language</string>
    <string name="select_language_item_selected_description">Selected</string>

    <string name="open_link_failed_title">Web page cannot be opened</string>
    <string name="open_link_failed_message">Web page cannot be opened because your phone does not have an internet browser or its use has been blocked.</string>

    <string name="power_rationale_title">Let Koronavilkku always run in the background?</string>
    <string name="power_rationale_message">Koronavilkku can check if you have been exposed to COVID-19 even while the app is closed. This requires disabling battery life optimisation for Koronavilkku.\n\nThe impact on your phone\'s battery life is minimal.</string>

    <string name="power_deny_confirm_title">Prioritised background activity disabled</string>
    <string name="power_deny_confirm_message">If you don\'t allow Koronavilkku to always run in the background, we recommend opening Koronavilkku manually at least once a day.\n\nYou can change this setting at any time in your phone\'s Settings.</string>
    <string name="power_allow_retry">Allow after all</string>

    <string name="exposure_check_error_title">Error loading exposure data</string>
    <string name="exposure_check_error_message">Exposure data could not be loaded. Please check your internet connection and try again.</string>

    <string name="share_consent_eu">Users of Koronavilkku and other European COVID-19 applications.</string>
    <string name="share_consent_finland">Users of Koronavilkku only.</string>
    <string name="share_consent_header">Who do you want to report your infection to?</string>
    <string name="share_consent_code_saved">Koronavilkku got your key code from a text message.</string>

    <string name="travel_disclosure_header">Have you travelled abroad within the past 14 days?</string>
    <string name="travel_disclosure_no">I have not travelled.</string>
    <string name="travel_disclosure_yes">I have travelled.</string>

    <string name="country_list_title">Where have you travelled?</string>
    <string name="country_selection_body">Which countries have you visited within the past 14 days? If the country you visited is not listed or you do not want to disclose it, select Other.</string>
    <string name="country_selection_other">Other</string>

    <string name="summary_consent_header">Confirm and send</string>
    <string name="summary_consent_continue">Enter your key code</string>
    <string name="summary_consent_body_eu">Information about your infection will be shared anonymously with users of Koronavilkku and other European COVID-19 applications.</string>
    <string name="summary_consent_body_finland">Information about your infection will be shared anonymously with users of Koronavilkku.</string>
    <string name="summary_consent_travel_header">Travel information</string>
    <string name="summary_consent_travel_body">You have visited these countries within the past 14 days:</string>
    <string name="summary_consent_travel_body_none">You have not travelled abroad within the past 14 days.</string>
    <string name="summary_consent_accept_header">Consent</string>
    <string name="summary_consent_accept_use">My encounter data and the estimated period of when I could have infected others may be shared with Koronavilkku for the purpose of breaking transmission chains.\n\nI give this consent voluntarily. My consent has not been required in a healthcare customer service situation nor in a procedure of authority.</string>
    <string name="summary_consent_accept_share">My encounter data, the travel information I have selected above, and the estimated period of when I could have infected others may be shared to COVID-19 applications used in the EU, EEA, Switzerland and the United Kingdom for the purpose of breaking transmission chains.</string>
    <string name="summary_consent_no_cancellation">Once you have sent the information, you cannot withdraw your consent.</string>

    <string name="notification_guide_title">If you receive an exposure notification follow these instructions</string>
    <string name="notification_guide_text_1">If you have been near a person who has reported their coronavirus infection via the application, you will receive a notification of potential exposure to your phone. Tap on the notification to open Koronavilkku.</string>
    <string name="notification_guide_text_2">Press the red See instructions button.</string>
    <string name="notification_guide_text_3">You will receive instructions on what to do. You will also receive instructions on how to contact a healthcare provider. Read the instructions and press the Contact button.</string>
    <string name="notification_guide_text_4">Select the municipality. You can contact the healthcare services via the contact methods provided by the municipality, such as via the Omaolo online service or by telephone.</string>
    <string name="notification_guide_text_5">The healthcare services will give you more detailed instructions and evaluate your need for a coronavirus test.</string>

    <plurals name="exposure_notification_count">
        <item quantity="one">%d notification</item>
        <item quantity="other">%d notifications</item>
    </plurals>

    <plurals name="all_count">
        <item quantity="one">%d pc.</item>
        <item quantity="other">%d pcs.</item>
    </plurals>

</resources>